Guide to the Newspaper Guild of New York Records WAG.125
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Early Records: General Files, 1935-1950
  - Newspaper Guild: Sacramento, California, 1939-1945 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Newspaper Guild: San Antonio, Texas, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Guild: San Francisco, California, 1939-1950 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Guild: San Jose, California, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Guild School, 1944-1945 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Guild: Seattle, Washington, 1939-1948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Guild: Shop Enforcement, 1943-1950 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Guild: Springfield, Massachusetts, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Guild: St. Louis, Missouri, 1941-1950 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild: Syracuse, New York, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild: Toledo, Ohio, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild: Toronto, Canada, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Guild: Tri-City in Albany, New York, 1945-1949 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Guild: Twin Cities, Minnesota, 1940-1948 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Guild: Union City, New Jersey, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Guild: Washington, D.C., 1939-1950 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Guild: Westchester, New York, 1934-1940 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Guild: Wichita, Kansas, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Guild: Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliveries Union, 1937-1943 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliveries Union: Strike, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 19a)
  - Newspaper Reporters Association, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Newsstand Dealers Union, Local 217, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - No-Strike Pledge, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Office: Accounts Payable, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Office: Staff, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Office: United Office and Professional Workers of America, 1939-1947 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Office of War Information, 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Officer's Files: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 26a)
  - Oil Workers Organizing Campaign, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Organizers Pool, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Organizing Assignments, 1942-1943 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Organizing Brochure, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Organizing Prospective, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Page One Ball, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Page One Delinquents (JED), 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Palestine, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Paper Handlers Union, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Pension Plans, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - People's Songs, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Personnel: Management Service, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Pledges for Picket Duty, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Pix, Inc.: Photographers, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Pittsburgh Courier, NY Office Organizing, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Post War Planning, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Postmaster General, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Potoker, M. Michael: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Pour la Victoire, 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Howell, Blanche v. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 45a)
  - Preferential Hiring, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Prentice Hall, Inc., 1949 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Press Release List, 1941 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Press Relations Committee of Harlem, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Progressive Citizens of America, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Price Roll-Back (Executive Order, April 10), 1943 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Public Guardian, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Public Relations (I), 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Public Relations (II), 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Public Relations (III), 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Public Relations (IV), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations (V), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations (VI), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations (VII), 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Publications (Guild Locals), 1941 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Publishers Association of New York City, 1939-1940; 1943 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Publishers Service: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Queens Pictorial Service, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaire Returns, Registered Labor Press, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Quigley Publishing: Associated Motion Picture Trade Journalists Union, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Quigley Publishing: Grievances, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Quigley Publishing: National Labor Relations Board, 1943- 1944 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Quigley Publishing: National Labor Relations Board, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Quigley Publishing: Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Quigley Publishing: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Quigley Publishing: Negotiations for Contracts, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Quigley Publishing: QP News, 1943-1946 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Quigley Publishing: War Labor Board Briefs (I), 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Quigley Publishing: War Labor Board Briefs (II), 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Quigley Publishing and Wid's Films v. Newspaper Guild, Local 3, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Quigley v. Local 3, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Quigley v. Local 3, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Quigley v. Local 3, Undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Radio Program: Free Speech, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Radio Program: New York Guild (I), 1943 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Radio Program: New York Guild (II), 1943 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Radio Program: New York Guild (I), 1944 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Radio Program: New York Guild (II), 1944 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Radio Program: WLIB, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Radio Program: WNYC, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 10a)
  - Radio Scripts, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Radio Stations, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Radio Unit Organizing, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Radio Writers Guild, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rainey, Dr. Homer P., 1944-1945 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Rally for America: Labor's Anti-Hitler Committee, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Re-Employment Conference, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Referendum: Per Capita, 1949 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Registered Unit, 1939-1941; 1950 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Remington Rand and United Electrical: Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Rent Control, 1944-1945; 1948 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Rental Account, 1941-1945 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Representative Assembly: Attendance, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Representative Assembly: Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Representative Assembly: General, 1943-1945 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Representative Assembly: General, 1948-1950 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Representative Assembly: Election of Chairmen, Ballots, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Representative Assembly: Minutes, 1939-1942 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Representative Assembly: Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Research Department: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Research Department: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Research Department: General, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Research Department: General, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Research Institute of America: Organizing Information, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Research Institute of America: Organizing Information, Undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Research Institute Staff: Policy Memorandum on Communism, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Resignations and Maintenance of Membership, 1941-1942; 1946 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Respectable Prostitute, Jean Paul Sartre, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Resorts, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Roman, John, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt Picture Paper, Election Campaign, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Russian War Relief, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Ryan, Jack F., 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis Post-Dispatch: Atrocity Murals, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Salaries, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sanitation Workers Organizing Committee, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Schappes, Morris, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Schneider, Edward, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - School for Brides, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Schools, 1939-1940 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Schuler, Jerome W., 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Screen Publicists Guild, 1940-1941; 1948 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Scripps-Howard Chain Council, 1943-1948 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Scripps-Howard Guild Advisory Council, 1939-1941 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Secretaries, 1944-1948 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Secretaries Meeting, Chicago, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Secretary-Treasurer: Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Seller, Richard H., 1943; 1946 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Service Bureau for Intercultural Education, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Shop Papers (Various), 1940-1949; 1954 (Box 24, Folder 28a)
  - Silverson, Frances, 1943-1944 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Social Security Board, 1940-1941 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Soviet Writers, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Staats-Zeitung und Herold: Clippings, 1940s (Box 24, Folder 31a)
  - Staff Meetings: Memos, 1943-1950 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Stampers Arrival of Buyers v. Newspaper Guild of New York (National Labor Relations Board), 1942 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Star: Employees, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - State Industrial Union Council, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Stern, Monroe, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Stewards, Shop Paper Editors, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Stowe, Leland, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Strike Clippings, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Taft-Hartley: CIO Analysis, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 4a)
  - Taft-Hartley: General, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Taft-Hartley: Procedures, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Taft-Hartley: Union Contracts, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Union of New York, Local 5, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Tickets, 1943-1948 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Time: Publicity, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Times Tower: Organizing, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Trade Union League of Ex-Servicemen, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Training School for Newspaper Workers, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Transport Workers Union, 1941; 1943 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Transport Workers Union: Negotiations, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Treasury Department: Wage Increase Applications, 1944-1945 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Triangle Publications: Arbitrations, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Triangle Publications: Correspondence, 1938-1947 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Triangle Publications: Guild Shop Election, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Triangle Publications: National War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Triangle Publications: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Tuck, Jay Nelson, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Twentieth Century Fox, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Twenty-Five Percent Wage Demand, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 23a)
  - Typographical Union, Local 6, 1933-1940; 1945 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Ukrainian Journalists, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Unemployed Guild Members, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1943-1944 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Unemployed Unit, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Unit: Chairmen, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Unit: Contributions to Pacific Coast Strike, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Unit: Grievance Committees, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Unit: Notices, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Unit: Reports on World Telegram and Sun Strike, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Unit: Reports on Grievance Procedures, 1947; 1950 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - United Automobile Workers, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - United Automobile Workers: General Motors Strike, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - United Electrical National: Public Affairs, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - United Features: Organizing, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - United Labor Committee, AFL-CIO, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - United Mine Workers, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - United Nations Appeal for Children, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - United Negro and Allied Veterans of America, 1947 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - United Packinghouse Workers, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1945; 1947-1948 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - United States State Department, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Up in Arms, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Veterans against Discrimination, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Veterans: Apprenticeship Training, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Council: Meeting and Organizing, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Veterans: Grievances, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Veterans: Groups and Organizations, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Veterans: Guild Vets!, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 9a)
  - Veterans: Information Bulletin, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Veterans: On the Job Training, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Veterans: Organizing, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Services: Information, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Voters Research Institute, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Wage Comparison, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 14a)
  - Wage and Hour Act, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Wage Stabilization, 1942-1943 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Wage Survey: Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Wages and Conditions in American Newspaper Guild Contracts, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - War Labor Board, 1942-1944 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - War Labor Board: Chicago Panel, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - War Labor Board: Maintenance of Membership, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - War Labor Board: Maintenance of Membership Hearings, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - War Labor Board: Regional Office, 1943-1944 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - War Labor Board: Retroactivity Policy, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - War Labor Board: Tripartite Advisory Committee, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - War Labor Board: Walker-Turner Case, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1943; 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - War Production Board: Newspaper Industry Advisory Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Washington Merry-Go-Round, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Washington Wage Conference (ANG), 1948 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Weilburg, John, 1944-1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Survey, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - West Side News and Town and Village, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Western Union Strike, 1945-1946 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Wheelock, Dorothy (Harper's Bizarre), 1943 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Wilkie, Wendell (Yorkshire Evening Post), 1943-1944 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Withholding Tax, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Work Projects Administration (WPA): General, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - WPA: Joint Committee to Defend WPA Workers, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - WPA: Living Issues Project, 1936-1939 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - WPA: Sylvan Pollock Case, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Worlds Fair, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Wright, Frederick Herzer, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Yiddish Writers Union, 1936-1937 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Yank, Sergeant Fred Rosen, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Young Children in Wartime, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - YMCA, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Yugoslav Relief Committee, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Series II: Early Records: Shop Files, 1935-1950
  Series II: Early Records: Shop Files, 1935-1950, documents shops organized in the early years of the NGNY, including those at the Brooklyn Eagle, Daily News, Herald Tribune, Journal American, Mirror, New York Post, New York Times, Newsweek, Time, and World Telegram.
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Minutes, 1940-1944 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Correspondence, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Negotiations, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Negotiations, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Negotiations, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Grievances, 1940-1947 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Shop Papers, 1939-1945 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Acme Newspictures, Inc.: Contracts, 1940-1941 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - American Weekly: Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - American Weekly: Minutes (Grievances Meetings), 1947-1949 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - American Weekly: Minutes, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - American Weekly: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - American Weekly: Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - American Weekly: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - American Weekly: Grievances, 1946-1950 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - American Weekly: Shop Papers, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - American Weekly: Contracts, undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - American Weekly: Clippings, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - American Weekly: Wage Re-Opening, 1947-1949 (Box 28, Folder 24a)
  - Amsterdam News: Minutes, 1941-1945 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Amsterdam News: Minutes, 1946-1949 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Amsterdam News: Correspondence, 1940-1947 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Amsterdam News: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Amsterdam News: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1942-1944 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances (Strike), 1946 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1947-1948 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Amsterdam News: Grievances, 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Amsterdam News: Shop Papers, 1943-1950 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Amsterdam News: Contracts, 1940-1948 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence (Kissling Case), 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence (Organizing), 1948-1949 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Associated Press: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1939-1940 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations (NWLB), 1946 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1946-1947 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Associated Press: Negotiations, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1944-1946 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Associated Press: Grievances, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Associated Press: Shop Papers, 1940-1946 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Associated Press: Shop Papers, 1940-1950 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Associated Press: Shop Papers, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Associated Press: Contracts, 1940-1944 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Associated Press: Clippings, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Aufbau: Minutes, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Aufbau: Correspondence, 1942-1948 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1940-1941 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1942-1944 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1945-1946 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1947-1948 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1948-1949 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Aufbau: Negotiations, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Aufbau: Contracts, 1941-1950 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Minutes, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Minutes, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (NANA, Associated Features & Consolidated), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Strike), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Strike), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Strike Charges), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Strike Publicity), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Strike Publicity – May), 1949 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Unit Job Description), 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Negotiations (Job Slotting Questionnaire), 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Contracts, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Shop Papers, 1948-1950 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - The Bell Syndicate: Clippings, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Billboard: Minutes, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Billboard: Correspondence, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Billboard: Negotiations, 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Billboard: Negotiations I, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Billboard: Negotiations II, 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Billboard: Negotiations I, 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Billboard: Negotiations II, 1945-1946 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Billboard: Negotiations, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 16)